stickeryou.com 2019-01-07

# Privacy Policy - StickerYou

StickerYou Inc. takes your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how StickerYou uses identifiable information regarding our customers, such as name, address, email address or credit card number ("Customer Information"). Primarily, we collect such information for the purpose of providing you with an outstanding experience on the StickerYou Service. Except as specifically described in this Privacy Policy, StickerYou does not sell, rent or share such Customer Information with third parties. 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 1st, 2010.

By using our Service, you consent to the collection and use of information in the manner described below. If we decide to change our privacy policy from time to time, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Changes to our policy will be prospective only. Please check this page from time to time for changes to make sure you are aware of our latest privacy practices. 

StickerYou is particularly sensitive to protecting information about children. Protecting children's privacy is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect information on our website from those children we actually know are under 13 years of age. In addition, no part of our website is targeted to attract anyone under 13 years of age. We request that children under 13 years of age do not disclose or provide any Customer Information. If we discover such information, we will delete the child's Customer Information from our records. If for any reason we believe a user may be under the age of 13 we reserve the right to request proof of age of such user. If such proof is not provided, or if it is discovered a user is under the age of 13, we will use best effort to delete from our servers and associated systems all Customer Information of that user and we reserve the right to limit and/or ban such user from our Website. Notwithstanding the foregoing, StickerYou encourages the use of its services by families. StickerYou also believes that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools, available from online services and software manufacturers, to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools may also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other Customer Information without parental permission. 

###  What Customer Information does StickerYou collect?

Customer Information is requested whenever you choose to purchase StickerYou products. The type of Customer Information we request has to do specifically with the type of service you are using. For example: 

When you want to order stickers from StickerYou, we will ask for your first and last name, a billing address, a shipping address, an email address, and a credit card number for the payment of developing, shipping and handling costs. 

When you complete a purchase from StickerYou, we will ask you to provide shipping and billing information so that we can fulfill your request. 

You also give information when you answer survey questions and organize your stickers on StickerYou with titles, captions, categories, etc. 

###  How does StickerYou use Customer Information? 

Our primary goal in collecting your Customer Information is to provide you with a personalized, relevant, user-friendly experience on the StickerYou site. 

We may use Customer Information to communicate with you and we consider this communication to be an integral part of the StickerYou service. We may use your email and mailing address to inform you of site improvements, feature announcements, newsletters, StickerYou promotional offers, and occasional third-party promotional offers that may be of interest to you. Only StickerYou (or agents working on behalf of StickerYou under confidentiality agreements) will send you these mailings. 

Note that one reason we are able to offer you relevant promotions is that we reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group. Your Customer Information, however, will never be personally identifiable when aggregated for these purposes. 

Consent to the collection, use and disclosure of Customer Information may be given in various ways. Consent may be express (e.g. orally, electronically or on a form you may sign describing the intended uses and disclosures of Customer Information) or implied (e.g. when you provide information necessary for a service you have requested (such as providing us with your name, phone number and/or email during the purchasing process), or in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your Customer Information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an "opt-out" option. Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian, person having a power of attorney or a mandatory). By providing us with Customer Information, we will deem you to understand this Privacy Policy, and we will deem you to consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such Customer Information for the purposes identified or described in this Privacy Policy, if applicable, or otherwise at the time of collection. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of Customer Information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice. Note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your Customer Information, we may no longer be able to provide you with certain of our products or services. 

###  With whom does StickerYou share Customer Information? 

StickerYou shares Customer Information with third party intermediaries who help us run the StickerYou Service and Site and with affiliated businesses that have licensed our sticker creation application and have created “stores” in their wesbites. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party. Otherwise, your Customer Information is provided to these third parties solely for the purpose of providing you the services you request at the time that you request them. 

Other than as described in the previous paragraph, StickerYou will not sell, rent or otherwise share Customer Information with a third party without your knowledge and consent. 

The one exception to the rule described in this section is the following: if StickerYou is required by law (or to protect its rights or property), we will disclose Customer Information to the extent so required. 

###  Who sees your stickers after they have been posted online? 

You and any friend you choose to email your stickers to. Also, StickerYou employees or employees of partner companies that provide services to StickerYou may see your stickers while they are developed or printed. In addition, your stickers or personal account information may be seen by StickerYou employees in order to evaluate, validate, or correct problems with your account. 

###  Does StickerYou use "IP Addresses" and cookies? 

StickerYou uses IP Addresses and Cookies in limited ways, as follows: 

IP Addresses: An IP address is literally your computer's address and is a unique identifier, allowing online information to be sent to the right place. We use IP addresses to better understand the customer database. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information such as geographic distribution of our members. We do not intentionally link your IP address to your personally identifiable information. 

StickerYou Cookies: Contrary to popular belief, cookies do not extract private or personal information from your computer's memory. The job of a cookie is to record only information you volunteer to us upon registering or visiting the site. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer the first time you visit our Web site that enable our server to recognize or "remember" who you are next time you come back. StickerYou cookies are not tied to personally identifiable information. Currently, StickerYou intends to make only limited use of cookies for the purpose of delivering content and ads specific to your interests. For instance cookies may be used to retain your personal preferences, hold session information for a "shopping cart" or save your password so it doesn't have to be re-entered each time you log in. 

Our website makes use of both “sessional” and “persistent” cookies. Persistent cookies are stored on your hard drive. Sessional cookies are stored in temporary (cache) memory and are deleted when you shut down your browser or turn off your computer. 

###  What are the safeguards and security procedures in place to protect your information from loss, misuse, or alteration? 

Your Information on our Service is password-protected. We strongly recommend that you do not give your password to anyone and that you change it every 3 months. You may edit your StickerYou account information by using your StickerYou member name and password. 

If you are using a public computer (public library, school computer, etc.) or a shared computer (family computer, roommate's computer, etc.), we strongly recommend that you sign out of your StickerYou account and close your browser before getting up and moving away from the computer. This will prevent others from accessing your account and personal information. StickerYou employs SSL - a specialized encryption and security technology -- to protect your Customer Information. We understand that this is especially important when there is an exchange of credit card, billing and password information. In addition, we limit access of Customer Information to only those employees who need it to carry out their jobs. 

StickerYou will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. 

You will only be asked for your member name and password when you initiate the contact and only if the member name and password are necessary to correct a service problem. 

We protect your Customer Information using physical, electronic or procedural security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information in our custody or control, including safeguards to protect Customer Information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification. StickerYou and its employees, servants, agents, contractors, legal, accounting or other service providers, partners, representatives and mandataries who require access to your Customer Information in order to fulfill their job requirements will have access to your Customer Information. You transmit or provide all Customer Information entirely at your own risk. 

###  How can you update or correct Customer Information? 

Customer Information that you provide during registration is available in your StickerYou online account. To edit your Customer Information, you must enter your username and password to access your account. You may edit your account information at any time. 

You can also cancel your StickerYou membership by writing [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) If you request cancellation of your account, StickerYou may (but is not required to) remove any and all Content (stickers), images or other personal information from the StickerYou site, and your stickers may not be accessible to you even if you choose to rejoin or reactivate your account at a later date. Information necessary for the purposes of maintaining business records regarding a cancelled account, including records of credit transactions and account ownership, will be retained in accordance with applicable law. 

Contacting StickerYou: If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at:
